virpus.com 2014-02-08

# Our Privacy Policy | Virpus

Virpus Networks is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Through the Internet, our primary goal is to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers and site visitors just looking for information.   

**Disclosure**

We do not disclose information about your individual visits with any other company. Information such as your name, address, email address, telephone numbers, etc. are not gathered or used by Virpus Networks or any of its partners. We do collect information from website submissions only. This information is limited to your email which is used to confirm submissions or notify of changes to listings that may affect a website within our directory. Virpus Networks may share such information in response to any legal processes, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. Otherwise, this information is kept in secure confidentiality. 

**Kids on Virpus Networks**

Virpus Networks takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of young people using our services, and encourages you to participate in your child's experience on the Internet. Virpus Networks is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children.

Virpus Networks recommends that parents review Virpus Networks's content and offerings before your child explores our website and use the various parental controls for children and the Internet found online. While we say this, we do not and will not have any adult content on this website.  

**Information**

The purpose of storing any personal information you may provide us when you visit our site or fill out any Virpus Networks forms, is to enable Virpus Networks to maintain communication with you. We will not sell, share, or give this information to any other company. Virpus Networks will only disclose user information to the proper authorities, when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

If we use cookies, it is only to help us serve you better. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Virpus Networks does not control these cookies or any other applications or tracking controls from other advertisers or partners of Virpus Networks.  

Remember that whenever you give out personal information on the Internet, that information can be intercepted in transit. While we strive to protect any personal information in our possession, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk except for on our secure pages. Virpus Networks will only receive credit card information over a SSL (secure encrypted) connection.   

By using this site, you agree to the Virpus Networks Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the Virpus Networks site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
